# HOANG NGUYEN

**Software Engineer** 

Bao960045@yahoo.com 226-260-8402 https://www.linkedin.com/in/ hoang-bao-nguyen/ https://github.com/hulos1995

#### **PROFILE**

Driven by a strong passion for software development, my career has been a journey of resilience, innovation, and growth. It's more than just a list of jobs – it's about overcoming challenges, grabbing every opportunity, and making a real difference.

#### **SKILLS**

- Html
- CSS
- Sass
- JavaScript
- REST
- APIs
- React JS
- Node.js
- MySQL
- Heroku
- TypeScript
- Oauth
- Agile Development

#### **PROJECTS**

### Full-stack Developer | StockiStash

JUL 2024, BRAINSTATION CAPSTONE

- Graduated capstone project.
- Full-stack application app with different roles, where user admin role is able
  to manage the inventory and other roles are able to see which items are
  related to their field of work and are able to add items to their cart.
- Skills used: React, Sass, Tailwind, Javascript, REST APIs, Node Express, MySQL, OAuth

# Front-end developer | Kijiji verification system

JUL 2024, BRAINSTATION HACKATHON

- Won 1<sup>st</sup> place as a collaborative team between Data Science, UX Design, and Software Engineering. Mimicked Kijiji website and created a verification page to support small Businesses.
- Skills used: React, Sass, Javascript

#### **EDUCATION**

# **BrainStation | Diploma, Software Engineering**

APR 2024 - JUL 2024, TORONTO, ON

# St. Clair College | Diploma, Mechanical Technician - CAD/CAM SEPT 2018 - JUN 2020, WINDSOR, ON

# St. Clair College | Diploma, Computer System Networking - Technician

SEPT 2014 - JUN 2018, WINDSOR, ON

#### **EXPERIENCE**

### Leader Mold Polisher | D&L Mold Inc.

AUG -2020 - APR 2024, WINDSOR, ON

- Trained more than 10 employees over four years, significantly improving team capabilities and overall performance.
- Ensured timely delivery of projects, resulting in increased client satisfaction and repeat business.
- Acquired three new clients by leveraging relationships with existing clients, expanding the company's customer base

#### Junior Mold Polisher | TL Mold Quality

JAN 2016 - AUG 2020, WINDSOR, ON

• Completed over 50 jobs, each requiring at least a week, consistently meeting deadlines and enhancing operational efficiency.

# Help Cook | Pho Maxim

APR - 2014 - JAN 2016, WINDSOR, ON

 Assisted with food preparation and serving, enhancing customer satisfaction and service efficiency